where do we
begin a year ago these uh cops and
lawyers
wouldn't dare cross any of you i mean
what happened
so what are you proposing it's simple
kill
the batman
here's my card
bruce this is harvey dent rachel's told
me everything about you
i certainly hope not
you always told me that we'd be together
did you mean it
bruce don't make me your only hope for a
normal life
you're alfred right that's right sir any
psychotic ex-boyfriends i should be
aware of
oh you have no idea
good evening ladies and gentlemen
we're tonight's entertainment well hello
beautiful
you look nervous
i've seen now would have to become to
stop men like him
the night is darkest just before the
dawn
i promise you the dawn is coming
and here we go
this city deserves a better glass of
criminal
i'm gonna give it to him no
we'll see i'll show you
you either die a hero or you live long
enough to see yourself become the
villain
will you be wanting the bat puncher in
the middle of the day alfred not very
subtle the lamborghini
much more subtle